<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>This flood alert remains in place. Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected. River levels are high and rising. Further rainfall is, however, forecast later this week and will keep river levels high. We are closely monitoring the situation and will update this message by 11:30AM on 17 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T10:35:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding remains possible.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue overnight, 16 December 2025, along the River Churn around Cerney Wick. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night and morning tomorrow, 17 December 2025, before persistent rainfall moves in tomorrow afternoon. Levels along the River Churn are currently stable. Levels are expected to rise further in response to forecast rainfall over the coming days.

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 09:00 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T19:20:20</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue overnight, 16 December 2025, especially in the along the River Windrush in the Bourton on Water, Newbridge and Standlake areas. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night and morning tomorrow, 17 December 2025, before persistent rainfall moves in tomorrow afternoon.River levels are rising very slowly upstream of Witney. Levels are currently stable in the Newbridge area. It is expected that levels will rise further in response to forecast rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T19:31:39</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected overnight, 16 December 2025, especially in the Moreton in Marsh and Shipton Under Wychwood areas on the River Evenlode. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night and morning tomorrow, 17 December 2025, before persistent rainfall moves in tomorrow afternoon. The rate of river level rise is decreasing, and levels along the River Evenlode are expected to stabilise overnight. It is expected that levels will rise further in response to forecast rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T19:33:22</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding remains possible .

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue overnight, 16 December 2025, along the River Thames, especially in the Kempsford area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night and morning tomorrow, 17 December 2025, before persistent rainfall moves in tomorrow afternoon. River levels are rising slowly in response to recent rainfall. It is expected that levels will continue to rise overnight. Levels are likely to rise further in response to forecast rainfall over the coming days. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 09:00 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T19:21:38</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue overnight, 16 December 2025, especially in the Bourton on the Water area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night and morning tomorrow, 17 December 2025, before persistent rainfall moves in tomorrow afternoon. River levels are currently falling slowly. It is expected that river levels will rise further in response to forecast rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T19:35:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding.

Flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible overnight, 16 December 2025, especially in the Lechlade area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night and morning tomorrow, 17 December 2025, before persistent rainfall moves in tomorrow afternoon. River levels are currently stable, but levels may rise again to recent rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T19:21:52</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tributaries on the Upper River Thames above Cricklade</title>
      <description>Rising river levels this evening may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 16 December 2025 . 
Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible, especially close to the Swill Brook in the Oaksey area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night and morning tomorrow, 17 December 2025, before persistent rainfall moves in tomorrow afternoon. We expect river levels to continue to rise slowly this evening before stabilising overnight. Levels may respond further to rainfall over the coming days. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded . 
This message will be updated by 9:00AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T19:05:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Middle Avon Rugby to Bidford</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible from the afternoon of 16 December 2025. Flooding may affect low-lying land and roads adjacent to the River Avon between Rugby and Bidford including Warwick, Stratford upon Avon, caravan parks and farmland. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T10:33:18</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Tributaries in Gloucester</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Further rainfall is forecast but no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T09:59:48</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Little Avon catchment and the Vale of Berkeley</title>
      <description>High river levels this morning may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 16 December 2025 . 
Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Little Avon, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around Areas most at risk include the Little Avon River and other rivers and streams in the Vale of Berkeley. Weather conditions are expected to improve this afternoon and no further flooding is expected. 
We are monitoring rainfall and river levels . 
Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses . 
This message will be updated by 10:30AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T08:31:33</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 16 December 2025. 

Flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgeley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. 

Predicted peaks:- 

Mythe 3.3m to 3.8m on 17/12/25 PM 

Haw Bridge 4.3m to 4.8m on 17/12/25 PM 

Sandhurst 2.8m to 3.3m on 17/12/25 PM 

Gloucester 2.7m to 3.2m on 17/12/25 PM. 

Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T07:48:28</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 16 December 2025.  Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Leadon. Locations that may be affected include Ledbury, Much Marcle, Staunton, Tibberton and Wedderburn Bridge may now be impassable. Water is over the road at Upleadon Court.  Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T07:26:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 16 December 2025. 

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. 

 Predicted peaks:- 

Evesham 1.7m to 2.1m on 17/12 AM 

Bredon 2.5m to 2.9m on 17/12 PM.  

Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T07:38:36</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Bristol Frome catchment</title>
      <description>High river levels this morning may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 16 December 2025 . 
Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Frome, Bristol Floating Harbour, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around Areas most at risk include St John's Way in Chipping Sodbury and Damson Bridge. Weather conditions are expected to improve this afternoon and no further flooding is expected. 
We are monitoring rainfall and river levels . 
Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses . The road may be flooded at Damson Bridge. 
This message will be updated by 10:30AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T08:31:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected overnight, 16 December 2025, particularly along the River Thamesbetween Lechlade and Shifford. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night and morning tomorrow, 17 December 2025, before persistent rainfall moves in tomorrow afternoon. River levels are rising slowly in response to recent rainfall. It is expected that river levels will rise further in response to forecast rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T19:35:23</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Rivers in the Forest of Dean</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 16 December 2025.  

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the river from Gloucester to Chepstow. Other locations that may be affected include Westbury and Lydney.  

Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water .  

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T07:29:21</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 16 December 2025.  

Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate closed at Upton upon Severn. 

Predicted peaks:- 

Bewdley 2.7m to 3.2m on 16/12/25 PM 

Worcester 3.0m to 3.5m on 17/12/25 AM 

Diglis 2.7m to 3.2m on 17/12/25 AM 

Kempsey Yacht Club 5.0m to 5.5m on 16/12/25 PM 

Saxons Lode 3.7m to 4.2m on 17/12/25 PM. 

Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T07:48:58</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding overnight. 
Flooding is expected on 17 December 2025 . 
Flooding may affect property and roads in and around Severn Ham and access to Abbey Mill may be compromised.

Predicted peak:- 
Mythe 3.3m to 3.8m on 17/12 PM. 
We are monitoring rainfall and river levels . 
Monitor local water levels and weather conditions . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 17 December 2025 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T16:20:42</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
