<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>River levels are stable at the Fosseway and Great Somerford gauges. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Further rain is forecast Monday and Tuesday. River levels are expected to rise further in response to this rain. We are closely monitoring the situation . Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 26 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-25T20:25:53</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Churn. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially near Cerney Wick.  Monday morning (26.01.26) and afternoon are expected to be mainly dry, but with rain from the early evening through to late morning or afternoon on Tuesday. Levels are likely to respond to this persistent rainfall and rise over the coming days

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T07:17:53</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Windrush. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, especially in the Newbridge area. Monday morning (26.01.26) and afternoon are expected to be mainly dry, but with rain from the early evening through to late morning or afternoon on Tuesday. Levels are likely to respond to this persistent rainfall and rise over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T07:20:06</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Windrush. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, especially in the Newbridge area. Monday morning (26.01.26) and afternoon are expected to be mainly dry, but with rain from the early evening through to late morning or afternoon on Tuesday. Levels are likely to respond to this persistent rainfall and rise over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T07:21:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>River levels remain high on the River Thames and its tributaries. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially near Hannington Bridge. Monday morning (26.01.26) and afternoon are expected to be mainly dry, but with rain from the early evening through to late morning or afternoon on Tuesday. Levels are likely to respond to this persistent rainfall and rise over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T07:26:47</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Dikler. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially in areas of Bourton on the Water close to the River Dikler. Monday morning (26.01.26) and afternoon are expected to be mainly dry, but with rain from the early evening through to late morning or afternoon on Tuesday. Levels are likely to respond to this persistent rainfall and rise over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T07:18:59</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>River levels remain high on the River Leach. Therefore, flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially in the Lechlade area. Monday morning (26.01.26) and afternoon are expected to be mainly dry, but with rain from the early evening through to late morning or afternoon on Tuesday. Levels are likely to respond to this persistent rainfall and rise over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T07:41:38</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high but steady today 26 January 2026 which may lead to flooding. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury may fill. Heavy rain is forecast over the next 24 hours which may lead to river levels rising further overnight and into tomorrow. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on Tuesday 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T09:22:42</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high but steady today 26 January 2026 which may lead to flooding. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. Heavy rain is forecast over the next 24 hours which may lead to river levels rising further overnight and into tomorrow. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on Tuesday 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T09:19:57</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and have a rising trend on the River Thames. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today near the river between Buscot Lock and Eynsham Lock. Monday morning (26.01.26) and afternoon are expected to be mainly dry, but with rain from the early evening through to late morning or afternoon on Tuesday. Levels are likely to respond to this persistent rainfall and rise over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T07:29:16</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>River levels today are high but steady. Flooding is possible on 26th January 2026. Heavy rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours which will likely lead to further river rises overnight into tomorrow.

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force.

Obersved Peaks:- 
Mordiford 3.9m 25/01 PM,  
Ross on Wye 3.45m 26/01 AM,

We are closely monitoring the situation.  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 27th January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T09:15:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels today are high but steady. Flooding is possible on 26th January 2026. Heavy rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours which will likely lead to further river rises overnight into tomorrow.

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. 

Observed Peaks:- 
Ross on Wye 3.45m 26/01 AM,  

Predicted peaks:-
Lydbrook 4.2m 26/01 AM, 

We are closely monitoring the situation.  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 27th January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T09:14:58</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high but steady today 26 January 2026 and flooding is possible. Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate closed at Upton upon Severn. Heavy rain is forecast over the next 24 hours which may lead to river levels rising further overnight and into tomorrow. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on Tuesday 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T09:16:41</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Coln and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from the morning of 26 January 2026 . 
Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected, especially in the Fossebridge area. Further heavy rainfall is forecast over the next 36 hours. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days. 
We are monitoring rainfall and river levels . 
Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded . 
This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 27 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T07:15:10</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
