<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>Rivers remain high and are now rising again due to rainfall.

Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels and checking rivers for blockages.

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Don't put yourself or others at risk.

This message will be updated by 10:30 AM on 15/12/2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T10:05:15</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding remains possible.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 15 December 2025, along the River Churn around Cerney Wick. The forecast is for showers developing today, 15 December 2025, particularly during the afternoon and overnight. Rainfall totals are not expected to be significant. Levels remain high but are starting to drop very slowly. We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days.

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 19:00 15 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T09:12:56</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 15 December 2025, especially in the Newbridge and Standlake areas. The forecast is for showers developing today, 15 December 2025, particularly during the afternoon and overnight. Rainfall totals are not expected to be significant. River levels remain high but are starting to fall very slowly. We expect levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 19:00 15 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T09:13:52</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, 15 December 2025, especially in the Woodstock area along the River Glyme. The forecast is for showers developing today, 15 December 2025, particularly during the afternoon and overnight. Rainfall totals are not expected to be significant. River levels have fallen below the flood risk threshold on the River Evenlode, and are now below the flood risk threshold along the River Glyme. Levels are expected to contiue falling, and further flooding is not expected in the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 19:00 15 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T09:14:08</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding remains possible .

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 15 December 2025, along the River Thames, especially in the Kempsford area. The forecast is for showers developing today, 15 December 2025, particularly during the afternoon and overnight. Rainfall totals are not expected to be significant. River levels are currently high and falling slowly. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 19:00 15 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T09:13:20</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, 15 December 2025, especially in the Bourton on the Water area. The forecast is for showers developing today, 15 December 2025, particularly during the afternoon and overnight. Rainfall totals are not expected to be significant. River levels are falling very slowly and back below the flood risk threshold along much of the River Dikler. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 19:00 15 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T09:15:30</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 15 December 2025, especially in the Lechlade area. The forecast is for showers developing today, 15 December 2025, particularly during the afternoon and overnight. Rainfall totals are not expected to be significant. River levels are high, but falling slowly. We expect levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 19:00 15 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T09:13:36</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 15 December 2025. River levels remain high due to recent rainfall. Flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. Recorded peaks:- Mythe peaked at 3.80m on Thursday 11/12/25 Haw Bridge peaked at 4.75m on Thursday 11/12/25. Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours which may see river levels rise further. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses . This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T08:22:17</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Further rainfall is forecast but no further flooding is expected.  
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-14T16:24:49</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, 15 December 2025, particularly along the River Thames in the Shifford area. The forecast is for showers developing today, 15 December 2025, particularly during the afternoon and overnight. Rainfall totals are not expected to be significant. River levels are falling steadily and along many parts of the River Thames are now below the flood risk threshold.  

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 19:00 15 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T09:16:03</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Further rainfall is forecast but no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T08:17:40</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
