<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Water regularly ponding on road, not reaching drainage ditch, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740672</link>
<description>The section of road between the railway bridge out Southam Lane and entrance to the race course. The verges are too high and water ponds on the road because it cannot reach the ditches quickly enough.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Southam Lane, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740672&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740672</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.93019 -2.054246</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Burst water main, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740640</link>
<description>Outside Roseville property. Burst main underground which flowing out of nearby manhole. Been like this for 2 weeks.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8740640.0.jpeg?25efccae&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 2, Shurdington Road, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740640&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>No rain in 24 hours - water has increased or remained the same</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740640</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.868497 -2.111003</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deep pothole on Pennsylvania Road, often unavoidable, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740572</link>
<description>North of Marchant close on right side of road. Often unable to avoid in car when driving due to cars parking on other side and it’s getting worse over time&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8740572.0.jpeg?c2f3687d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 43, Pennsylvania Avenue, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740572&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740572</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.909891 -2.104174</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Repeated blockages of road drain, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740560</link>
<description>This drain is blocked again, the resulting flood completely blocks the pedestrian crossing point. This crossing is used by hundreds of children every day going to and from Lakeside School. This morning I had to help a visually impaired lady cross the road here as her guide dog rightly would not lead her through the water. There has been no rain for hours and yet there is still over a metre wide flood here. This drainage has been a persistent problem for years but has never been satisfactorily fixed.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 263, Hatherley Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740560&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740560</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.889099 -2.116285</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lauriston Park Cheltenham nos 38 The Island with overhanging trees, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740532</link>
<description>Our Area as you can see is cleared of all vehicles allowing your team to access the the island outside 38 Lauriston park cheltenham .Yesterday they came and went there were no cars around the island apart from one mini .I took the photos yesterday and they didn’t come back saying they had to get more equipment .Hopefully it will be done today .Cross our fingers .Its been so difficult to get our neighbours to cooperate.So thank you 🙏 and please come today&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8740532.0.jpeg?f9fe6987&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Merlin Way, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740532&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740532</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.882503 -2.087563</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large pothole as you approach bridge, 401 Swindon Road Cheltenham, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740517</link>
<description>Large pothole as you approach to go over bridge on Swindon Road, heading towards booker and funky warehouse. Been there for days and still unpainted, is a danger and now I have a completely punctured a tyre&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tewkesbury Road, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740517&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740517</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.910274 -2.093617</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large pothole just off the speedbump, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740302</link>
<description>Nearside travelling west just off speedbump. Another really bad one further up too. Surprised my tyre didn&amp;#39;t blow out.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 24;26, Libertus Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740302&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740302</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.898633 -2.104082</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Numerous pot holes along the road, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740210</link>
<description>These pot holes are getting bigger and bigger and in avoidable these will damage a vehicle&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Village Road, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740210&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740210</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913797 -2.106418</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Several potholes in Church Road, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740170</link>
<description>As you turn off Hyde Lane onto Church Road there are several deep potholes which are difficult to avoid hitting.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Plus there is another large pothole when you turn off Church Road onto Quat Goose Lane.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;These are busy areas as the primary school is on this road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hyde Lane, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740170&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740170</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.923189 -2.089051</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole getting bigger, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740135</link>
<description>Whilst heading north, the pothole is very near the first traffic calming section. Forcing both north and south bound traffic to drive through it. It&amp;#39;s getting bigger every day.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;There are also several smaller potholes opening up along this road to the south of this pothole&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 119, Village Road, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740135&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740135</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913975 -2.106247</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Metre long stretch of potholes, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740134</link>
<description>Driving down Hyde Lane away from Bishops Cleeve opposite the new build house with the long driveway there are several deep potholes about a metre long in total. Larger vehicles have to drive on the wrong side of the road to avoid them.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hyde Lane, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740134&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740134</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.924897 -2.083871</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fencing blocked path, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740009</link>
<description>Entrance to bridleway from A4019. The major work being done (presumably to widen the A4019) means a lot of fencing has gone up. Originally it was still possible to access the path/Bridleway that leads up to the church, but now the gap has been chained and padlocked. I walked down from the church and found myself trapped within the fencing.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tewkesbury Road, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740009&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Obstruction caused by fence</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8740009</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.92701 -2.134072</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Two large 50cm deep pot holes, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739866</link>
<description>Park lane on right hand side road before you arrive at Brockhampton Deer Park on the right hand side&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Park Lane, Sevenhampton, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739866&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739866</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.899993 -1.956458</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Drain blocked solid, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739815</link>
<description>Opposite garages near in between flats and the red bricked stand alone house number 2 Lansdown Place Lane. Needs clearing out please.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8739815.0.jpeg?193dd8bd&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 71, Lansdown Crescent Lane, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739815&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739815</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 05:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894792 -2.087116</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Now becoming impossible to pass and if you hit this will cause damage to vehicle, 22nd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739784</link>
<description>In middle of road by disable bay. Been there about a month but is now really deep. In the dark not easy to miss and even in daylight now as it is very deep and getting wider daily&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 16, Yarnolds, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739784&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739784</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 05:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.865338 -2.116894</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Small pile of asbestos roofing, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739499</link>
<description>A pile of roofing, which appears to be corrugated asbestos has been left on the side of the road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Oxenton, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739499&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739499</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.972563 -2.077109</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deep pothole at the top of Badgeworth bridge, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739480</link>
<description>There is a really deep pothole towards the left side of the road as we reach the top of the bridge driving from Badgeworth towards Reddings. As the road narrows at this point, drivers trying to avoid the pothole are having to veer right straight onto oncoming traffic, and both sides have no visibility of each other at this point. This could result in a serious accident anytime. I had a near miss today. I’m aware that this bridge has had multiple fixes in recent years. However we’ve now seen a number of potholes appearing again up and down the bridge slopes. Please could you inspect and fix these urgently as this is a main thoroughfare and a bus route.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Badgeworth Road, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739480&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739480</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.884252 -2.142579</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deep pothole on Grovefield way at pedestrian crossing, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739466</link>
<description>There is a deep pothole at the pedestrian crossing on Grovefield way on the left carriageway while driving from Arle court towards Symphony road. This is situated just before turning left into Symphony road. The position of the pothole is towards the right side of the crossing and it caused damage to my car’s front right tyre and wheel rim. I request you to kindly check and fill this pothole at the earliest.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Grovefield Way, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739466&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739466</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.884916 -2.131429</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Huge gigantic big crater, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739449</link>
<description>Big crack in the road, pretty soon we will need a bridge to get over it. Almost broke the front end of my partners car&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Andover Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739449&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739449</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.893105 -2.089916</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Series of potholes on Badgeworth bridge, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739445</link>
<description>There are a series of potholes at the bottom of the slope of the Badgeworth bridge on the left carriageway while travelling from Badgeworth towards the Reddings. The camber on the road and oncoming traffic forces vehicles to drive straight into these potholes, resulting in damages to the front left tyres. Please could you inspect these and fix the road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Badgeworth Road, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739445&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739445</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.886137 -2.142778</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>