<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Only street light in the close is off, pitch black, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488631</link>
<description>The only Street light in Japonica Close is not coming on. Its pitch black outside. Outside number 9.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Japonica Close, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488631&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488631</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.888105 -2.189626</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dropped kerb dangerous, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488548</link>
<description>The dropped kerb outside 101 Dinglewell is very unsafe and rocky. My elderly grandparents live here and I’m worried for their safety. My grandad is living with Alzheimer’s and is registered blind so this needs to be fixed promptly.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Kingscroft Road, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488548&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The kerb is damaged/missing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488548</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.853145 -2.191182</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Danger petrol station on Waitrose premises, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488474</link>
<description>Car Wash Waitrose Complex, Honeybourne Way, Cheltenham GL50 3QW Waitrose &amp;amp; Partners Cheltenham GL50 4EZ Look at the fault underneath same as electric anything can chip. The Government&amp;#39;s allowed Indian Pakistan with White Foreigner take over all the petrol station. Investigate how many profit they made. Who&amp;#39;s petrol station?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Shell Honeybourne Way, Cheltenham GL50 3QW? 01242 254633. Look in to employment if Indian pakistan using legacy to pass it on. Use White people Program to achieved their goals working paying bills rent providing for mother and father with kids. So none notice who is health and safety if becomes manager supervisor now gets employed speaking on your company behalf. Premises customer. See the danger why plant getting out of control. They understand to scanned the leafs on earth still bearing when winter an can keep it spreading underneath. Use Road Worker pretend digging up the roads adding new dirts. Switch direction the root growing zigzag across. This is what imagine by seeing it twist up on the building. They understand electrical wire install an petrol tank under the ground. Remember have have warned ⚠️. Please report immediately Rishi Sunak an Indian pakistan plus bangladesh white Muslim foreigner. Using money transfer understand if can move Country they free nothing they did wrong. Now is the time made Government investigate none of the overseas resident care about the environment all they after is compensation wish bad on others they find the risk. Walking under bridge, crossing, tower blocks elevator, Aeroplane travelling, vehicle, motorbike can think in the mind as an wish but they controlled the steering with they hands. Use they feet step on the acceleration gass. They find the mind as an weapon both vehicle can use purpose blame on they fault politicians, cycling schoolter both can have spite set it up to blame if do not wants to live when enjoy sex as much eat as much buy expensive things go on, holiday have kids. How it feel live as poor prisoner? When it is one life. Can you find death understand think if knows how humans can comes back alive after them can kill as animals an see how government can gets them back alive. They find cannot die but rather test another person wants all in the Crowd find that purpose hate the Majesty family if Government is nothing why give Indian pakistan permission an wants to destroy they life. In the cold plus free benefit Claim why all of them working check they bank account. How many kids buy they house investment private businesses.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please take off all the homeless people if the population of human being is so much NHS giving up free pregnancy in labour unlimited no restriction of each family members. Free school, free college. How it feel now wants Indian pakistan do anything for money an can pay for university fee. Plus buy houses have all private businesses are they living life hard. Henry working on the Street Sweeper landlord Indian pakistan paying him £680 a month he told if come off benefit increase rent expensive. He bought, the house. Consort Lodge, 3 Consort Rd SE15 2PH. They pretend poor having it hard before becomes rich all of them help each other use sings if give away gifts can made enjoy hiding for sex an use spite do the same that is how wants to pass on legacy riches in they family an after government in permission to destroy others in the risk as how teaching they kids use fault purpose if someone inspecting your brain. Think as movie work out all the ideas to made up the faults for the worst life accident Crime by depressed worry hate argument fight hold things against. Plus if don&amp;#39;t wants to live use Churchs speaking to God now speak in mind as test to see if no one can stop them hold weapons in the kitchen. Test if the person eat the food, think could of poison. Think of sex hands cleaning baby passing on virus for addiction. Test if attempted see if can hear them as voices. Might be radio tv channel can tease the person in public not have to be under mental health. Lobby video game stream. That is what they found the law showing them to joined take advantage as playing against computer football, call of duty. If bring it in reality they find no one believe not bring it to Court no Confession use think they experience trick fool destroyed they life wants it bigger with intention 3 life sentence; voices 1, ringing noise 2, something as an insect came through the tv channel an got in they body 3. Wants to use this against&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8488474.0.jpeg?ea6e0952&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 35, Market Street, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488474&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488474</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904062 -2.085702</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rocky dropped kerb, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488301</link>
<description>The dropped kerb outside 101 Dinglewell is very rocky and needs to be bedded back in. My elderly parents live at this address and this is a welfare issue as my father is blind and has dementia. This has been an issue well over a year and has been reported, but nothing has been done.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Kingscroft Road, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488301&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The kerb is damaged/missing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488301</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.853115 -2.191193</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>All drains either blocked or not adequately draining - large pools of water causing drenched pedestrians, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488293</link>
<description>Both sides of the pedestrian crossing have inadequate drainage meaning water pools for a long time. This affects both sides of the road by the pedestrian crossing as well as outside the entrance to the vets. I have seen cars / lorries drench multiple pedestrians including school children and older adults.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road East, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488293&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488293</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.886479 -2.188868</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The light is dull outside numbers 41 and 43 wymans road lamp post number is 6, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488250</link>
<description>Outside number 41 and 43 wymans road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 37, Wyman&#39;s Road, Whaddon, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488250&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light is dull</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8488250</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.906141 -2.057588</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potholes, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487940</link>
<description>Lots of damage and potholes on this road now mainly northbound side&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cleeve Road, Gotherington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487940&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487940</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.958876 -2.054486</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pavement floods regularly, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487819</link>
<description>Next to the traffic island on the Providence Park side of the road, pavement completely floods every time it rains. There is no drain here, so the water remains for days.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 46-61, Princess Elizabeth Way, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487819&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487819</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.911095 -2.102505</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Traffic lights are failing, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487774</link>
<description>The temporary traffic lights on lobleys drive and Lobleys road in Brockworth are failing.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The main traffic lights at the crossroads at a Gambet rd are also failing because of backed up traffic and people having skipped lights. Lights are only remaining on for up to 5 seconds and that’s it. There is backed up traffic in all directions&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gambet Road, Brockworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487774&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light sensor is not detecting vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487774</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.841235 -2.17675</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Builders’ waste in front of the garage block, on the highway and pavement/service strip, restricting access to garages and communal parking area. Periodically waste is partially removed but never completely, and has been an issue since the first full week of September this year. Reporting it now as wet and windy conditions over the past few days have resulted in several items being blown across the cul de sac and the soil turning into a ‘river’ of mud on the road and inconveniencing other residents. The waste is not covered and at night there are no lights suggesting that this use of the highway is not licensed., 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487705</link>
<description>In front of garage block opposite Bramble Cottage, 9 Gwinnett Court, Shurdington GL51 4GQ&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8487705.0.jpeg?820fabd9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 7, Gwinnett Court, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487705&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487705</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.865681 -2.113329</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Drains on N bound A435 seem to be all blocked, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487474</link>
<description>Ran alon A435 Sat morning - heavy rain. ALL the drains appear blocked from bulding dirt etc&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Evesham Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487474&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487474</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.927124 -2.068283</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loose manhole cover outside Royal Oak pub, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487416</link>
<description>Manhole cover in road outside Royal Oak pub is loose and extremely noisy when traffic runs over it.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 58, Hucclecote Road, Hucclecote, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487416&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487416</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.857084 -2.192448</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unpermitted roadworks problem, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487501</link>
<description>Road closure sign left behind, no works were actually done.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487501&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Unpermitted roadworks</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487501</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.875405 -2.09309</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light is permanently out problem, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487500</link>
<description>One SL is out, this has been like this for over 4 weeks and though it would be sorted by now.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487500&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487500</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.854483 -2.131852</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Serious visibility hazard due to parking too close to corner, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487269</link>
<description>Vehicles are parking too close to the corner, causing a dangerous reduction in visibility for drivers entering or exiting the street. Given the constant, high traffic flow due to the road being a major cut-through, this visibility obstruction presents a safety risk.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Albemarle Road, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487269&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Car parking</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487269</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878582 -2.163203</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>TMC - Defects -CW6 Potholes  problem, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487315</link>
<description>Give and take 28 day plus  15  minutes delay boards carriage way pothole  400x300x450mm tarmac parch  stats required (CW6 Pothole)&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487315&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>TMC - Defects -CW6 Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487315</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.881399 -2.1130957</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overhead bridge, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487095</link>
<description>31B Market St, Cheltenham GL50 3NJ Door 26 this is the 2 houses landlord are the council giving resident tenancy. None report the serious danger. Of the walk way Bridge plus the open park night at night. I saw an Indian female with an Indian pakistan guy walking late. Testing something in they body. If can use location Henry wanted to pee. Wants to prove he getting them horny find ideas think. They find mind to live in an TV Channel Using secret law is impossible unbelievable what they done behind they parents find it Shameful how can tell the truth. Now is the time give them justice. If the Indian Pakistan had an little sister 9 year old an he is about 16 years old. He find white people can do the same. Why none not being the bigger one an set a better example. They live off them. Investigate and see the proof Tesco Subway Sainsbury. Look around areas Indian pakistan be next to Chinese restaurant. King an Queen streets roads, Princess an Prince Royal Mail, Petrol Station, Burger King, KFC, McDonald&amp;#39;s, jobcentre with Muslim Optician hospital courthouse. Both Police Station Indian pakistan with white people an soldiers camp hide in all different country university. Promoting Rishi Sunak is part of White Using pakistan bangladesh white Muslim foreigner in that country. Look if only be doctor consultant with White. Look if Rich have all the Private Businesses phone contract dealership cars internet network. Work in the airport have private business train station. Now look if they speak about it are just pretend working with white people. Look if none homeless work in the cold for years. Check out 1 an 2 if do no work just hide in years. Find security african look if they hide not showing white they living off. Look if speak about the mind. Put on News look in to Rishi Sunak family all around honour appreciate expose to the whole world. What His Majesty King Charles III did give them chances an opportunity becomes Prime Minister an have all private businesses over poor black just wants population on benefit. Using application an he rich turn them down like this Using millions can apply for the rules.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please inspect if Indian pakistan mixing they kids with white Check out all over United Kingdom see if Rishi Sunak expose his family have 2 daughter is he strict. He cannot bring it to Court Henry wants doctor Check his 2 daughter vagina if he cannot expose Queen Elizabeth II family son an daughter. How many time Henry wants him in court if not writing his life story he Check his 2 daughter vagina before over 18. If he do not wants to check Henry 3 cousin vagina is that not right? Why wants Southwark Council with the mother suspects gets old without take it in court. See why Henry spreading it around anytime can report. He might come across. Why not giving him justice. Would you not check the 3 daughter vagina? Now Henry wants daughter to check his 2 daughter vagina. If Rishi Sunak cannot bow honour show David Cameron an Boris johnson Barack Obama if not an good government destroy his life to think evil planned plot. He do not wants Henry found out did he wrote his full life story an face King Philip an Queen Elizabeth II? He wants him think work out an hold it against accuse offended he got to tell the truth. He in government none listen ignore lie no matter if have sense put him down no understanding&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8487095.0.jpeg?dae89f33&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 35, Market Street, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487095&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487095</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904062 -2.085702</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light not working opposite 11 Bramble Rise, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487088</link>
<description>Street light not working opposite 11 Bramble Rise - noticed about a week ago&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 11, Bramble Rise, Noverton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487088&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487088</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.908183 -2.042644</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Road surface deterioration dangerous to cyclists, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487073</link>
<description>The nearside of the road cycling down Harp Hill is deteriorated with multiple potholes and surface defects. This is approached on a bike at speed and is dangerous to cyclists. If you hit the uneven surface on a bike you risk losing control. If you avoid the surface problems you are pushed out into the middle of the road with fast moving traffic. Please could you resurface this piece of road in one even continuous patch. Thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8487073.0.jpeg?2fe744e1&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Harp Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487073&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487073</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.898649 -2.045653</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Water accumulates when it rains and makes people have to go out into a busy road to get to the pavement, 1st December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487062</link>
<description>In the road opposite Deans Way Bishops Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8487062.0.jpeg?3cf57e98&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Deans Way, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487062&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8487062</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.944076 -2.061493</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>